很久以前，我們的銀河系被統治
Long ago,
our galaxy was ruled
來自一個叫伊瑞德人的外星種族
by an alien race
called the Eridians
其力量和技術
whose power and technology
遠遠超出了人類的理解範圍。
were far beyond
human comprehension.
儘管它們很久以前就消失了，
Though they disappeared
ages ago,
他們留下了一些技術碎片，
they left behind fragments
of their technology,
成為基礎的廢料
scraps that became
the foundation
促進人類的進步。
for all human advancement.
但埃瑞德人最大的秘密
But the Eridians'
greatest secrets
藏在保險庫裏
were hidden in a vault
位於潘多拉星球。
located on the planet Pandora.
曾經和平的世界被企業佔領，
The once peaceful world
was overrun by corporations,
罪犯，
criminals,
- 和尋寶者... -槍，槍，槍！
- and treasure seekers...
-Guns, guns, guns!
互相爭鬥、互相殘殺
...fighting
and killing one another
以獲得找到保險庫的機會。
for a chance to find the vault.
但它仍然隱藏著。
But it remained hidden.
然後，在一片混亂之中，
Then, amidst
the clouds of chaos,
一線希望的光芒閃現。
a glimmer of hope
shone through.
一個預言。
A prophecy.
那一天，
That one day,
埃裏迪亞的女兒會打開保險庫
a daughter of Eridia
would open the vault
並恢復這個破碎星球的秩序。
and restore order
to the broken planet.
是的。
Yeah.
這聽起來像是一些瘋狂的廢話，對吧？
That sounds like
some wacko B.S., right?
嗯，我也這麼認為，直到......
Well, I thought so too,
until...
發生了這樣的混亂。
this mess happened.
他就在那兒！
There he is!
停止！
Stop!
該死的！
God damn!
那裏沒有氣孔。
There's no air holes in there.
真是一頂愚蠢的頭盔。
What a stupid helmet.
蒂娜.
Tina.
嘿。
Hey.
我是羅蘭。
I'm Roland.
是的。有一些，呃……
Yeah. There's been some, uh...
出了一些麻煩。
There's been some trouble.
阿特拉斯
And Atlas,
他派我來帶你到安全的地方。
he sent me
to bring you to safety.
- 我爸派你來的？ - 沒錯。
- My dad sent you?
- That's right.
他最矮的士兵是？
His shortest soldier?
是啊，他最矮的士兵
Yeah, his shortest soldier
去拯救他最不搞笑的女兒。
to save his least
funny daughter.
代碼三安全漏洞。
Code three security breach.
該站處於封鎖狀態。
The station is in lockdown.
所有人員必須就地避難。
All personnel
must shelter in place.
- 好的，我們走吧。 - 嘿，嘿，嘿！
- Okay, let's go.
- Hey, hey, hey!
- 我們放慢速度。- 目標在望！
- Let's slow down.
-Target in sight!
來吧，來吧。
Come on. Come on.
停止！
Stop!
趴下！
Stay down!
- 噢，天啊。 - 不，不！
- Oh, God.
- No, no!
抓住。
Catch.
假衝鋒隊員婊子。
Fake stormtrooper-ass bitch.
到這兒來。
Come here.
代碼三安全漏洞。
Code three security breach.
來吧，來吧。
Come on. Come on.
該站目前已被封鎖。
The station is now in lockdown.
等一下，我改變主意了。帶我回牢房。
Wait, I changed my mind.
Take me back to my cell.
- 請你這樣做。- 來吧。
- Please.
- Come on.
天啊！一個精神病患者逃出來了。
Holy shit!
One of the Psychos got out.
是時候瘋狂了！
It's time to go insane!
你在我的位置上了。
You're in my spot.
放他下來，放他下來。
Put him down. Put him down.
嘿，簡單。
Hey, easy.
你怎麼了，呃…
What do you, uh...
你覺得我可以和你做朋友嗎？
What do you say
me and you be friends?
拉屎。
Shit.
抱歉，諾克斯。
Sorry, Knoxx.
我的女孩。
My girl.
克裏格，發生什麼事了，夥計？
Krieg,
what's up, man?
你想要一些煎餅嗎？
You want some pancakes?
我的女孩心碎了。
My girl broken.
是克裏格吧？
It's Krieg, right?
是的。
Yeah.
你能幫我把她救出來嗎？
What do you say you help me
get her outta here?
是的。
Yeah.
當然，
Of course,
我們不可能都是埃利迪亞的女兒，
we can't all be
the daughter of Eridia,
沿著命運的道路跳躍。
skipping down
the path of destiny.
我們中的一些人必須工作來謀生。
Some of us
have to work for a living.
你不必這麼做，你知道。
You don't have
to do this, you know.
我的意思是，我可以付錢給你。
I mean, I can pay you.
是的，現在我錢包裏的東西都是你的。
Yeah, whatever's in my wallet
right now, it's yours.
好的？
Okay?
閉嘴，不然我就打斷你的另一隻胳膊。
Shut up
or I'll break your other arm.
哦，不，一隻手臂就好。
Oh, no,
one arm's good.
沒關係。
That's fine.
-怎麼了？- 抱歉。
-'Sup?
- Sorry.
- 奎因。 - 莉莉絲。
- Quinn.
- Lilith.
你知道，我們確實還有其他座位。
We do have other seats,
you know.
這樣，他就可以輕鬆地找到它了。
Then he won't have
any trouble finding one.
呃，今晚不行。
Uh, not tonight.
頂層架子。
Top shelf.
不確定您認為架子有多高。
Not sure how top
you think the shelves are.
呃，給你的孩子買一些舞蹈課。
Eh, buy your kid
some dance lessons.
熱門約會？
Hot date?
你還記得上個月在萊克特拉城發生的搶劫案嗎？
You remember that heist down
in Lectra City last month?
是的，有幾名警衛死亡。
Yeah, a couple of guards died.
是啊，這個可悲的傢伙就是槍手。
Yeah, well, this sad sack
was the trigger man.
聽著，我從來沒想過要射殺任何人。
Listen, I never meant
to shoot anyone.
我當時……
I was...
我已經太老了，不適合做這種事。
I'm getting too old
for this shit.
賞金獵人？呃。
Bounty hunting? Uh.
這是給年輕和愚蠢的人準備的。我說得對嗎？
It's for the young and stupid.
Am I right?
你真的想讓我回答這個問題嗎？
You really want me
to answer that?
我沒有。
I do not.
莉莉絲。
Lilith.
滾開。
Piss off.
我聽說你是個脾氣暴躁的老頭……
I heard you were quite
the crusty old...
等一下。等一下，等一下。
Wait. Wait, wait.
我們，呃，也許一開始就犯了錯誤。
We, uh, maybe got off
on the wrong foot.
你看，嗯...
You see, um...
我代表一位非常富有的人
I represent a very wealthy man
誰有與你的合同。
who has a contract for you.
我有工作。
I've got a job.
也許下個月吧。
Maybe next month.
你收集那些渣滓
You collect on that scum
是死是活，對嗎？
dead or alive, right?
嘿。
Hey.
別在這裏，大個子。
Not in here, big boy.
我們不想惹任何麻煩。
We don't want any trouble.
只是，我們的僱主並不是一個喜歡等待的人。
It's just, uh, our employer
is, uh, not one for waiting.
誰是？
Who is?
你是跟這些混蛋一夥的嗎？
Are you with these assholes?
或者你只是暴力的愛好者？
Or are you just a fan
of violence?
這些先生們工作
These gentlemen work
或者我應該說對我「有用」？
or should I say "worked" for me?
我會讓金伯來清理這個。
I'll get Kimber
to clean this up.
謝謝，奎因。
Thanks, Quinn.
這真是令人印象深刻。
That was impressive.
我警告他們不要低估你。
I warned them
not to underestimate you.
我的名字是 Deukalian Atlas。
My name is Deukalian Atlas.
還有，呃...
And, uh...
堅持，稍等。
Hold on.
這是...
This is...
這確實有些尷尬。
This is rather awkward.
嘿，你在那兒。
Hey, you there.
胖小子。
Fat boy.
把我放上去。
Put me on.
但她剛剛殺了弗蘭克和韋斯。
But she just
killed Frank and Wes.
但她絕不會向你這樣有實力的人開槍。
But she would never
shoot a man of your caliber.
毫米。
Mm.
正如我所說的……
As I was saying...
開始行走。
Start walking.
我的名字是 Deukalian Atlas。
My name is Deukalian Atlas.
總統...
President of the...
阿特拉斯公司？
The Atlas Corporation?
名字裏有線索。
Clue's in the name.
瞧，呃，這真是漫長的一天。
Look, uh, this has been
a really long day.
我們可以直接跳到
Can we just skip to,
我不知道，這是什麼？
I don't know, whatever this is?
當然。
Of course.
我的女兒被綁架了，
My daughter has been kidnapped,
我需要她回到我身邊。
and I need her returned to me.
賞金獵人，不是保姆。
Bounty hunter, not babysitter.
您沒有可以發送的玩具士兵嗎？
Haven't you got some
toy soldiers you can send?
是的，深紅之槍。
Yes, the Crimson Lance.
不幸的是，綁架者就是其中之一。
Unfortunately, the kidnapper
is one of them.
我需要一個局外人。
I need an outsider.
知道如何處理行星的人
Someone who knows
how to handle a planet
充滿了精神病患者、混蛋和金庫獵人
full of Psychos, skags,
and vault hunters
就像他們出生在那裏一樣。
like they were born there.
你女兒在潘多拉上嗎？
Your daughter's on Pandora?
思念和祈禱。
Thoughts and prayers.
但你付給我的錢不夠
But you couldn't pay me enough
再次踏上那片鬼地方。
to set foot
on that shithole again.
你確定嗎？
Are you sure about that?
哦。
Oh.
也許你可以。
Maybe you could.
好的，我將在現有合同結束後開始工作。
Okay, I'll start
when my current contract ends.
看來您可以立即開始。
Seems like you're free
to start immediately.
把信標給她。
Give her the beacon.
當你找到我的女兒時激活這個裝置
Activate this device
when you find my daughter
我的人民將會把她救回來。
and my people
will retrieve her.
到目前為止你還沒有令我失望，莉莉絲。
You haven't disappointed
so far, Lilith.
我勸你不要開始。
I advise you not to start.
對不起。
Sorry.
媽的。
Oh, shit.
感謝您駕駛 Atlas 運輸艙。
Thank you for
flying Atlas transport pods.
您已抵達目的地。
You've arrived
at your destination.
潘多拉。
Pandora.
讓我告訴你你需要知道的一切
Let me tell you
everything you need to know
關於潘多拉。
about Pandora.
這簡直就是個糞坑。
It's a shithole.
我應該知道。我來自這裏。
I should know. I'm from here.
天哪，我討厭這個星球。
God, I hate this planet.
這是一個地方
It's the kind of place
你永遠不想再回去。
you don't ever wanna return to.
所以，我越早找到那個女孩，
So, the sooner I find the girl,
我就能越快離開這裏。
the sooner I can
get the hell outta here.
這名士兵劫持了阿特拉斯的一架航天飛機
The soldier had hijacked
one of Atlas' shuttles
幾個月前就墜毀在這裏。
and crash-landed here
months ago.
剩下的不多了。
There wasn't much left of it.
它被拆成幾部分
It'd been stripped for parts
並遭到金庫獵人的破壞。
and vandalized
by vault hunters.
根本不知道他和蒂娜是否還活著。
No way to know
if he and Tina even survived.
想知道你是否見過她。
Wanna know if you've seen her.
但後來我和一些當地人交談過。
But then I spoke
to some locals.
拾荒兒童勉強維持生計。
Scavenger kids
barely scraping out a living.
他們告訴我蒂娜和士兵
They told me
Tina and the soldier
幾周前就已經通過
had passed through weeks ago
向北朝 Fyrestone 行駛。
heading north
towards Fyrestone.
然後我遇到了一些其他當地人。
Then I ran
into some other locals.
跑步！
Run!
精神病患者、兇殘的團伙。
Psychos.
Murderous gangs.
是時候搭車向北走了。
It was time to catch a ride
and head north.
你好，秘藏獵人。
Hello, vault hunter.
需要搭車嗎？
Need a ride?
是的，我不是一名秘藏獵人，但是......
Yeah, I'm not
a vault hunter, but...
歡迎加入。
Then welcome aboard.
裏面有人，上面有袋子。
People inside, bags up top.
不需要任何炸藥爆炸。
Don't need
any explosives going pop.
相信我，那真是太糟糕了。
That is a mess to clean up,
believe me.
您好，乘客。
Hello, passenger.
我叫馬庫斯。
My name is Marcus.
當然，
But of course,
你來這裏不是為了閒聊的。
you're not here for small talk.
你來這裏是為了尋找保險庫。
You are here to find the vault.
呃，你可以停在那裏。
Uh, you can stop there.
不是秘藏獵人。
Not a vault hunter.
只需要搭車。
Just need a ride.
如果你這麼說的話。
If you say so.
你好，勇敢的秘藏獵人。
Well, hello,
brave vault hunter.
所以，你來這裏是為了尋找
So, you've come in search
伊瑞德人失落的秘密寶庫，
of the secret lost vault
of the Eridians,
就在潘多拉這裏！
right here on Pandora!
您想變得富有到超乎想像嗎？
Do you want to be rich
beyond your wildest dreams?
首先，你必須找到鑰匙，
First, you must find the keys,
然後是保險庫本身，但這並不容易。
then the vault itself,
but it won't be easy.
你能把這個狗屎關掉嗎？
Could you turn this shit off?
不是秘藏獵人。
Not a vault hunter.
沒有辦法。
No can do.
這輛巴士是用來運送金庫獵人的，所以……
This bus is for transporting
vault hunters, so...
您會是找到保險庫的人嗎？
Will you be
the one to find the vault?
充滿高科技秘密的古代外星寶藏......
Ancient alien treasure filled
with high-tech secrets...
潘多拉是一個危險的地方，
Pandora is a dangerous place,
所以你需要更強大的火力。
so you need superior firepower.
準備好馬庫斯的一枚彈藥。
Prepare yourself
with one of Marcus' munitions.
下一站，Fyrestone，
Next stop, Fyrestone,
所有秘藏獵人的起點。
where all vault hunters begin.
呃，不。
Uh, no.
真的，我不是...
Really, I am not...
謝謝。
Thanks.
祝你好運，秘藏獵人。
Good luck, vault hunter.
我希望你能找到你在尋找的東西。
I hope you find
what you're searching for.
經過兩周的跋涉，
Two weeks on the trail,
天氣如潘多拉的衛星一樣寒冷。
and it was as cold
as Pandora's moons.
蒂娜和士兵早已不見蹤影。
Tina and the soldier
were long gone.
我需要一個奇跡，但我得到的卻是別的。
I needed a miracle,
but I got something else.
我的眼睛！
My eye!
你射中了我的眼睛！
You shot me in my eye!
你讓我失去了生命的意義！
You blinded me for life!
我該如何生存下去？
How will I manage to survive?
我只是在開玩笑！
I'm just kidding!
我被設計來抵禦各種暴力行為，
I was designed to withstand
all kinds of violent acts,
甚至像你這樣的完全不合理的。
even completely
unjustified ones like yours.
現在，我猜你一定想知道，
Now, I bet you're wondering,
這是怎麼回事？
what's the deal with this thing?
呃，不，我不是這樣的。
Uh, no, I'm not.
我天生幽默，
I'm programmed for humor,
所以我會將其理解為「詼諧的玩笑。」
so I will process that
as "witty banter."
打敗它。
Beat it.
我是 Hyperion 品牌 CL4P-TP，
I'm a Hyperion brand CL4P-TP,
可能是我這個種族中最後一個仍在服役的人了。
possibly the last of my kind
still in service.
但你可以叫我...
But you can call me...
哎呀！哈！
Whoopsie! Ha!
你又不小心射到我的臉上了。
You accidentally shot me
in the face again.
正如我所說，你可以叫我 Claptrap。
As I was saying,
you can call me Claptrap.
你知道，我可以整晚這樣做，
You know,
I can do this all night,
所以滾開。
so piss off.
相信我，我希望我能
Believe me,
I wish I could
根據我所經歷的一點點
based on what little
I've experienced
你的可怕個性。
of your horrendous personality.
但我別無選擇。
But I have no choice.
你是什​​麼意思？
What do you mean?
是 Atlas 派你來的嗎？
Did Atlas send you?
阿特拉斯？真噁心！
Atlas? Yuck!
我不為競爭對手工作。
I don't work
for the competition.
不，我一直躺在垃圾堆下
No, I've been lying dormant
under a garbage heap
算起來...是...36年！
for... calculating... 36 years!
但當你踏上潘多拉星球的那一刻，
But the moment
you landed on Pandora,
我被重新激活了
I was reactivated
因為我已經被編程來在你回來時幫助你！
because I've been programmed
to help you upon your return!
沒有人知道我要來這裏。
No one knew I was coming here.
就連我也沒有。
Not even me.
誰給你編程了？
Who programmed you?
我不知道！
I don't know!
這很可惜，因為你是個糟糕的人
Which is a shame,
because you're an awful person
我很想知道這事該怪誰。
and I'd love to know
who to blame for this.
既然我沒有，我別無選擇，只能為你服務
Since I don't, I have
no choice but to serve you
直到你死去。
until you're dead.
這聽起來像是威脅嗎？抱歉。
Did that sound like a threat?
Sorry.
反正只要你還沒死，
Anyway, as long as
you're not dead,
- 我來幫忙。 - 哦
- I'm here to help.
- Oh.
而且我有很多技能。
And I have many skills.
平衡。
Balancing.
轉圈圈。
Turning in circles.
我不需要伴侶。
I don't need a partner.
呃，我也可以訪問 ECHOnet。
Uh, I can also access
the ECHOnet.
您說的是「ECHOnet」嗎？
Did you say "ECHOnet"?
你能用它找人嗎？
Can you use it to find someone?
當然。只要給我看一張照片就行。
Of course.
Just show me a picture.
我會入侵並搜索
I'll hack and search
它的火柴視覺庫正在慢慢消亡
its slowly dying
visual banks for matches
並找到目標的最後已知位置。
and find your target's
last known location.
找到她。
Find her.
她最後一次出現是在 Fyrestone 外面。
She was last seen
outside Fyrestone.
正在訪問網絡。
Accessing network.
♪ 掃瞄，掃瞄，掃瞄 ♪
♪ Scanning, scanning
Scanning ♪
♪ 掃瞄，掃瞄，掃瞄 ♪
♪ Scanning, scanning
Scanning ♪
♪ 掃瞄，掃瞄，掃瞄 ♪
♪ Scanning, scanning
Scanning ♪
♪ 掃瞄，掃瞄，掃瞄 ♪
♪ Scanning, scanning
Scanning ♪
不唱歌你能做到嗎？
Could you do it
without the singing?
是的！
Yes!
♪ 掃瞄，掃瞄，掃瞄 ♪
♪ Scanning, scanning
Scanning ♪
完畢！
Done!
您的目標上次被記錄
Your target was last recorded
靠近苔原快車上的一個廢棄採石場！
near an abandoned quarry
in the Tundra Express!
步行只需132天
It's only 132 days on foot
有 98% 的幾率被 Craw 蛆蟲吃掉！
with a 98% chance of being
eaten by a Craw maggot!
我喜歡這些幾率！
I like those odds!
我們需要一些輪子。
We're gonna need some wheels.
那是紅色長矛，阿特拉斯的私人軍隊。
That's the Crimson Lance,
Atlas' private army.
他們在這裏幹什麼？
What are they doing here?
哦，只是猜測。
Oh, just a guess here.
和你做的一模一樣。
Exactly the same thing
you're doing.
蘭斯 (Lance) 和 Psychos 聯手了嗎？
And the Lance
teaming up with the Psychos?
看來 Atlas 會聘請
It seems like Atlas will hire
幾乎每個人都找到了他的女兒。
just about anyone
to find his daughter.
正在集中注意力。抱歉。
Concentrating.
Sorry.
嗯。蘭斯一家要走了。
Huh. The Lance are leaving.
我猜他們沒有找到她。
I guess they didn't find her.
沒有媽媽了！
No more Mommy!
免費午餐！熱賣中！
Free lunch! Hot delivery!
嗯？
Huh?
拯救這些孩子的行為太不合常理了。
That was so out of character
to save those children.
好吧，我需要搭車。
Well, I needed a ride.
有一瞬間，
For a second there,
我以為你不是一個可怕的人。
I thought you weren't
a horrible person.
呼！世界又恢復正常了。
Phew! The world
makes sense again.
現在前面只剩下一個位置了，
Now, there's only room
for one up front,
但不用擔心。
but worry not.
我可以坐在你的腿上。
I can sit on your lap.
莉莉絲！
Lilith!
你不小心把我鎖在後面了！
You accidentally locked me
in the back!
莉莉絲！
Lilith!
請耗盡我的電池。
Please drain my battery.
讓我回去睡覺。
Put me back to sleep.
我不會說的。
I won't tell.
你說過你想幫忙。
You said you wanted to help.
我說我被設計來幫忙。
I said I'm programmed to help.
我想要做的是抹去我的記憶，
What I want to do
is wipe my memory,
你這個可怕的女魔頭。
you horrendous she-devil.
您確定這些是正確的坐標嗎？
Are you sure these
are the right coordinates?
是的。這是你獵物的最後已知位置。
Yes. This is the last known
location of your quarry.
得到它？
Get it?
但看起來她現在已經走了很久了。
But it looks like
she's long gone by now.
是嗎？
Does it?
你知道，這裏有著相當多的動物園。
You know, it's quite
a menagerie you've got here.
您可以建立自己的潘多拉動物園。
You could start
your own Pandoran zoo.
你一定是蒂娜。
You must be Tina.
名字叫莉莉絲。
Name's Lilith.
那麼，那個士兵……
So, that soldier...
誰帶你來這裏，
who brought you here,
他也在玩捉迷藏嗎？
is he playing
hide-and-seek, too?
他離開了我。
He left me.
我好幾天沒見到他了。
I haven't seen him in days.
好吧，我來接你回家
Well, I'm here to take you home
給你的父親。
to your father.
是的，他看起來真是一個可愛的人。
Yeah, he seems like
a real, uh, sweetheart.
啥？我爸爸？
What? My daddy?
我能見到我的爸爸嗎？
I get to see my daddy?
真的嗎？
Really?
我一直很害怕。
I've been so afraid.
- 是啊。- 我很害怕。
- Yeah.
-I've been scared.
說到你的爸爸……
Speaking of your daddy...
外面的響聲確實把我嚇壞了。
The noises outside
really freaked me out.
我只是想讓他知道我保證你安全……
I've just gotta let him know
that I got you safe...
我應該去拿我的東西了。
I should probably
get my stuff.
拉屎。
Shit.
我真的愛我的爸爸。
I really love my daddy.
他是一位如此富有愛心的父母形象。
He's such a nurturing
parental figure.
當然，我必須相信你的話。
Sure, I'll have to take
your word for it.
莉莉絲小姐，
Miss Lilith,
你能抓住我的 Badonkadonk 嗎？
can you grab my Badonkadonk?
你現在什麼？
Your what now?
你這個小...
You little...
我很喜歡賞金獵人的來訪。
I love it
when bounty hunters drop by.
是時候下雨了……
Time to make it rain...
用你的身體部位。
with your body parts.
嘿。
Hey.
你還活在下面嗎？
You still alive down there?
她看上去精神錯亂了。
She seems deranged.
你們倆有很多共同點。
You two have a lot in common.
只是她更小、更漂亮、更可愛。
Only she's smaller,
nicer, cuter.
希望那不是什麼重要的事情。
Hope that wasn't
something important.
修復此問題。
Fix this.
因為，哇，它完蛋了。
Because, whoo, it's toast.
你去哪了？
Where'd you go?
蒂娜.
Tina.
看，我......我來救你了。
Look, I... I'm here to save you.
我看上去像是需要拯救的樣子嗎？
Do I look like
I need saving?
因為我在這裏
'Cause I'm up here
你們都躲在車底下。
and you're all hiding
under a car.
像個母狗！
Like a bitch!
你現在就下來。
You get down here right now.
哦，戰爭！
Oh, Krieg!
這個花哨的女人
This fancy-ass woman
剛剛用槍指著你最好的朋友。
just pointed a gun
at your best friend.
我會舔乾淨你的脊椎。
I will lick
your spine clean.
和精神病患者一起躲起來了嗎？
Holed up with Psychos?
他只是曾經是一個精神病患者。
He only used to be a Psycho.
現在他是我的哥哥！
Now he's my big brother!
多麼甜蜜啊。
How sweet.
你們其中一個人殺了另一個人，我要去喝杯咖啡。
One of you kill the other,
I'm gonna go get a coffee.
告訴她她贏得了什麼，克裏格。
Tell her what she's won, Krieg.
你遛錯了狗。
You've walked
the wrong dog.
朝他的臉開槍。
Shoot him in the face.
再次朝他的臉開槍。
Shoot him in the face again.
它不起作用。忘掉它。放棄。走吧！
It's not working.
Forget it. Abort. Go!
快跑！快跑！
Run, run!
我的更大一些。
Mine's bigger.
聽。
Listen.
我是你父親派來的。
I was sent by your father.
嗯，這很奇怪。
Well, that's strange.
因為女士，我沒有父親。
Because I don't
have a father, lady.
我知道這個星球可能會擾亂你的思緒。
I know this planet
can mess with your mind.
我的思維很奇妙。
My mind is awesome.
我的頭腦太酷了。
My mind's so cool.
聽著，我不想待在這裏。沒什麼私人恩怨。
Listen, I don't wanna be here.
Nothing personal.
所以如果你能跟我一起去
So, if you could
just come with me,
你可以和你爸爸談談
and you could talk to your dad
你們可以解決這個問題，
and you guys can sort it out,
家庭風格。而且我可以……
family style. And I can...
幹得好，女士。你直接把他們引向了我。
Nice work, lady.
You led 'em straight to me.
於是，阿特拉斯派了新的人去尋找這個女孩。
So, Atlas sent
someone new to find the girl.
從來沒想到這是一個卑鄙的金庫獵人。
Never would have thought
it was a scumbag vault hunter.
實際上，我並不是一個卑鄙的金庫獵人。
Actually, I'm not
a scumbag vault hunter.
事實上，她是個卑鄙的賞金獵人。
Actually,
she's a scumbag bounty hunter.
你知道，你工作不順不是我的錯，
You know, it's not
my fault you suck at your job,
無論你是誰。你是誰？
whoever you are. Who are you?
深紅之槍的指揮官諾克斯。
Commander Knoxx
of the Crimson Lance.
我要帶著這個女孩一起走。
And I'm taking the girl with me.
哦，是嗎？
Oh, yeah?
你和哪支軍隊？
You and what army?
就在我身後那個。
The one right behind me.
動起來，動起來。
Move, move.
查理隊，右側。
Charlie team, right side.
跟著你，跟著我！
On your lead, with me!
跟在我身後。
Stay behind me.
- 我去。 - 等一下。
- I'll go.
- Wait.
如果你們都很友善，
And if you're both nice,
我要向爸爸說幾句好話。
I'll put in a good word
with Daddy.
我覺得聽起來不錯。
Sounds good to me.
魯索中士，
Sergeant Russo,
給我給那女孩拿來一個神經項圈。
bring me a neurocollar
for the girl.
收到，指揮官。
Copy that, Commander.
領子？
A collar?
我喜歡新珠寶。
I love new jewelry.
是的，我也給你買了一份禮物。
Yeah, I got you a gift, too.
抓住。
Catch.
你願意做我的朋友嗎？
Will you be my friend?
媽的！
Oh, shit!
是的！
Yes!
- 來吧！ - 嘿！
- Come on!
- Hey!
媽的！
Oh, shit!
蒂娜！
Tina!
停下來。她要跟我一起去。
Stop.
She's coming with me.
我讓你獨自一人待10分鐘......
I leave you alone
for 10 minutes...
上車。
Get in the car.
沒關係，他和我在一起。
It's okay. He's with me.
我希望我不是這樣。
I wish I wasn't.
上車！
Get in the car!
走吧，走吧！
Go, go!
莉莉絲，等等我！
Lilith, wait for me!
我告訴你什麼了？
What did I tell you?
最小爆炸。
Minimal explosions.
不，我說了不要爆炸！
No, I said no explosions!
你到底是誰？
Who the hell are you?
這是莉莉絲。是我爸爸派她來的。
This is Lilith. My dad sent her.
哦。她是個卑鄙的賞金獵人。
Oh. She's a scumbag
bounty hunter.
不，我是一名高級賞金獵人，朋友。
No, I am a high-end
bounty hunter, pal.
-不 -而且讓孩子們挨槍子
-No.
- And letting kids get shot at
不屬於我的工作職責。
was not part
of my job description.
噢，我敢打賭不是這樣的。
Oh, I bet it wasn't.
莉莉絲。莉莉絲。
Lilith. Lilith.
你不經意間把你最好的朋友落下了！
You inadvertently left
your best friend behind!
去死吧！
To die!
莉莉絲！
Lilith!
動起來，動起來，動起來！
Move, move, move!
嘿！別有壓力
Hey!
No pressure or anything
但我很想進來，
but I'd love to come inside,
- 如果你有機會的話。- 你在做什麼？
- if you get a chance.
- What are you doing?
我只是希望你能伸出手來，把我抱起來。
Just hoping you can
reach out and scoop me up.
你不必停下來，只是...
You don't have to stop, just...
嘿！
Hey!
對商品要寬容一些。
Go easy on the merchandise.
他們來了！
Here they come!
所有部隊，現在你們可以自由使用武器了！
All units,
you are now weapons free!
把他們拿下！
Take them down!
該死！你知道嗎？
Damn it! You know what?
你開車。
You drive.
你被編程來掌舵嗎？
You programmed to steer?
誰？我？
Who, me?
誰在駕駛這輛該死的卡車？
Who's driving the damn truck?
♪ 開車，開車，開車 ♪
♪ Driving, driving, driving ♪
♪ 我開車技術真好 ♪
♪ I'm so good at driving ♪
♪ 我是一名機器人司機 ♪
♪ I'm a robot driver ♪
鎖定目標，女士。
Locking on target, ma'am.
我們遇到問題了！
We got a problem!
做好衝擊的準備！
Brace for impact!
神聖的內衣！
Holy underwear!
我讓你開車的。該死。
I told you to drive. Damn it.
土匪一號，四號，在右邊。切斷他們。
Bandit one, four,
up on the right. Cut 'em off.
他們把我們困住了。
They got us pinned.
還沒有。稍等一下。
Not yet they don't. Hold on.
— 做好準備。— 你在做什麼？
- Brace yourselves.
-What are you doing?
那是個糟糕的想法
That was a terrible idea
但它確實起作用了。
but it worked.
嗯，也許吧。
Mm, maybe.
我們在哪裏？
Where are we?
沖溝小溝。
Pisswash gully.
那是什麼味道？呃。
What's that smell? Ugh.
- 把窗戶關上。 - 為什麼？
- Put the window up.
- Why?
把窗戶打開！
Put the window up!
那是什麼味道？
What is that smell?
大家談論的「氣味」到底是什麼？
What is this "smell"
thing everyone talks about?
- 聽聽我剛才說的話！ - 我不想！
- Listen to what I just said!
- I don't want to!
- 把窗戶搖上來！ - 不要告訴我該怎麼做……
- Roll the window up!
- Don't tell me what to...
它就在我的嘴裏！
It's in my mouth!
沙丁魚雨。
Sardine showers.
這是尿。這是尿。
It's pee. It's pee.
現在我把尿都灑在卡車中間了。
Now I got pee
all in the middle of my truck.
更正一下。67% 是尿液……
Correction.
It's 67% urine...
14% 糞便...
14% fecal...
—哦！—小心！
- Oh!
-Look out!
噢，天哪！
Oh, God!
誰也別動。
Don't nobody move.
我並不想就此死去……
I'm not about to die in this...
住口。
Shut up.
好的。
Okay.
那是……
Is that...
這看上去不太好。
This don't look so good.
是的。
Yes, it is.
那東西看起來很生氣！
That thing looks angry!
- 你想按倒車鍵嗎？ - 或者餓了。
- Do you wanna press reverse?
-Or hungry.
噢，天啊。這會要了我們的命。這會要了我們的命。
Oh, my God. It's gonna kill us.
It's gonna kill us.
等一下。
Wait a second.
您要我按「反向」鍵嗎？
Do you want me to press reverse?
不，我不想你什麼都不做！
No, I don't
want you to do nothing!
我的天啊！
Oh, my God!
你的朋友們回來了。
Your friends are back.
羅蘭，別傻了。
Roland, don't be stupid.
只要把女孩給我們就行了。
Just give us the girl.
大家繫好安全帶。我有一個計劃。
Everybody, buckle up.
I got a plan.
誰來抱抱我！
Somebody hold me!
說真的，我沒有系安全帶！
Seriously, I have no seat belt!
羅蘭，你在做什麼？
Roland, what are you doing?
— 快走，快走，快走！— 堅持住！
- Go, go, go!
-Hold on!
- 稍等！- 不，不，不！
- Hold it!
-No, no, no!
拉屎。
Shit.
感覺就像我們爆胎了。
Feels like we blew a tire.
你把這稱為計劃嗎？
You call that a plan?
它成功了，不是嗎？
It worked, didn't it?
請隨意鼓掌。
Feel free to applaud.
耶，沒死！
Yay for not dying!
沒有什麼。
Nothing.
- 你留在這裏守望。- 好的。
- You stay here and keep watch.
-Okay.
但他們似乎不信任你。
But it's you
they don't seem to trust.
誰又能責怪他們呢？
And who can blame them?
♪ 掃瞄，掃瞄，掃瞄 掃瞄 ♪
♪ Scanning, scanning, scanning
Scanning ♪
他們現在應該正在追我們​​。
They should be after us by now.
如果沒有地面支援，黃貂魚就不會進行追擊。
Stingrays won't pursue
without ground support.
諾克斯將等待增援。
Knoxx'll wait on reinforcements.
放下吧，大個子。
Let it down, big guy.
在你把綁架寫進簡歷之前
Before you added kidnapping
to your resume
您是 Crimson Lance 的一名軍官。
you were an officer
in Crimson Lance.
正確的？
Right?
羅蘭沒有綁架我。他救了我。
Roland didn't kidnap me.
He saved me.
救了你什麼？
Saved you from what?
輕鬆富足的生活？
A life of ease and plenty?
我爸爸以為我是埃利迪亞的女兒。
My daddy thinks
I'm the daughter of Eridia.
我可以打開保險庫。
I can open the vault.
金庫？
The vault?
這就是這件事的來龍​​去脈？
That's what this shit is about?
你把她偷走了。
You stole her for yourself.
現在你知道死了多少人嗎
Now, do you know
how many people have died
正在尋找泥土中的那個洞嗎？
looking for that hole
in the dirt?
嗯，我知道。
Well, I do.
我的母親就是其中之一。
My mother was one of them.
我們擁有他們沒有的東西，寶貝女兒。
We have something they don't,
baby girl.
哦，讓我猜猜。什麼？精神？
Oh, let me guess. What? Spirit?
敢做敢為的態度？友誼的力量？
Can-do attitude?
The power of friendship?
有良心。
A conscience.
無論保險庫裏有什麼，
Whatever's in that vault,
像阿特拉斯這樣的人永遠也無法得到它。
a man like Atlas
can never get his hands on it.
- 好吧，羅蘭，冷靜下來。- 不！
- All right, Roland, calm down.
-No!
她是一名為阿特拉斯工作的卑鄙賞金獵人。
She's a scumbag bounty hunter
who works for Atlas.
怎麼，你認為你的快樂英雄團隊可以阻止他嗎？
What, and you think your band
of merry heroes can stop him?
哦，我們可以試試。
Oh, we can try.
我們在做這件事的時候不能小心謹慎。
We just can't watch our backs
while doing it.
所以，幫我個忙。拿起你的武器。
So, do me a favor.
Take your weapon.
把它扔過來。
Toss it over here.
拿上一些補給，出去走走。
Grab some supplies, take a walk.
你知道，當阿特拉斯發現那裏有派對時，
You know, when Atlas finds out
about that party back there,
我已經跟死了一樣。
I'm as good as dead.
所以，不管喜歡與否...
So, like it or not...
我們是站在同一邊的。
we're on the same side.
我想補充的是，這是一支沒有軍隊的一方。
A side without an army,
I might add.
所以我希望你有一個比
So, I hope
you got a better plan than
駛入脫粒機的咽喉。
driving down
a thresher's gullet.
不。
No.
但我知道有人這麼做。
But I know someone who does.
一位科學家、一位保險庫專家。
A scientist, a vault expert.
救出蒂娜並拿回鑰匙是她的主意。
It was her idea to break
Tina out and collect the keys.
按下一個鍵，還剩兩個鍵。
One key down, two more to go.
當然還有我。
And, of course, me.
加載。
Load up.
下一站，庇護之城。
Next stop, Sanctuary City.
好的！
All right!
公路旅行！
Road trip!
好的，戴上面具。
All right, mask up.
我們想保持低調。
We wanna keep a low profile.
市場清淡。
Market clear.
複製一下。
Copy that.
哦，這個地方確實變了，
Oh, this place
sure has changed,
變得更糟。
for the worse.
後退。後退！ 前往 23 號登機口。
Back off. Back off!
Heading to Gate 23.
噢，我的天。
Oh, my.
這位帥氣的魔鬼是誰？
Who's this handsome devil?
他是一個惡毒的殺手。
He's a badass killer.
懸賞金額剛剛漲到 15 萬美元。
And the reward's
just gone up to 150 grand.
看起來你不是
Looks like you're not
唯一特別的一個，孩子。
the only one
that's special, kid.
食人蛙大會！
Cannibal frog convention!
好的，我們到了。
Okay, so we're here.
現在該怎麼辦？
Now what?
我需要找到我的聯繫人。
I need
to locate my contact.
莫西會知道如何找到她。
Moxxi will know how to find her.
莫西？
Moxxi?
是的。你認識她嗎？
Yeah. You know her?
是的，有點。
Yeah, kind of.
我的意思是，已經有一段時間了。
I mean, it's been a while.
你能變成一個洋娃娃並抱著它嗎？謝謝。
Would you be a doll
and hold this? Thank you.
克裏吉！載我一程。
Kriegy! Give me a ride.
嘿。
Hey.
我們盡力保持低調。
We're trying to stay low-key.
嘿。你找到了嗎
Hey. Did you find
您在 Fyrestone 中尋找什麼？
what you were looking for
in Fyrestone?
從未見過你，陌生人。
Never seen you before, stranger.
很好的嘗試，Vladof Infinity 小姐。
Nice try, Miss Vladof Infinity.
我永遠不會忘記槍。
I never forget a gun.
你現在在做什麼呢，非秘藏獵人？
What are you up to now,
Not-A-Vault-Hunter?
她正在尋找金庫。
She's vault hunting.
我就知道。
I knew it.
我告訴過你，我知道。
I told you, I knew it.
好，好，好。
Well, well, well.
看看那條 skag 拖了什麼東西進來。
Look what the skag dragged in.
—嘿，莫克斯。—快進來吧。
-Hey, Mox.
- Get on in there.
哦，不用客氣。
Oh, you are most welcome.
為我的小甜心準備的奶昔，
Milkshake for
my little sugarplum,
還給我的朋友們喝了點酒。
and drinks for my friends.
我有東西要給你看。
I got something to show you.
大家快過來。
Everyone, come over here.
走進我的辦公室。
Step into my office.
羅蘭？
Roland?
—羅蘭。—我明白了。
- Roland.
-I got it.
打擾一下。
Excuse me.
我知道是你。
I knew it was you.
- 噢，天哪。- 嘿，拉裏。
- Oh, my God.
-Hey, Larry.
你可能不記得我了，但是
You probably
don't remember me, but
我當然記得你。
I sure remember you.
你的媽媽是一位好女人。
Your mama was a good woman.
是啊，嗯，不知道。
Yeah, well, wouldn't know.
好的。那麼，這位呃科學家在哪裏？
All right. So,
where is this, uh, scientist?
所以，這就是你要去的地方。
So, this is where you're headed.
你一路走上樓梯
You go all the way
up those stairs
電梯就在那裏。
and right there is the elevator.
-嗯哼。-按下按鈕。
-Mm-hm.
- Push the button.
Passcode 的「ECHO」。
Passcode's "ECHO."
- 回聲？ - 回聲。
- ECHO?
- ECHO.
你確定呆在那裏安全嗎？
You sure it's safe
to stay there?
是的，只要這個人不炸毀這個地方就行。
Yeah, as long as this one here
don't blow up the joint.
那邊的奶昔怎麼樣，親愛的？
How's that milkshake there,
sugar pie?
聽。
Listen.
無論它值多少錢……
For whatever it's worth...
我真的很高興你回家了。
I'm real happy
that you came back home.
我希望你知道你的媽媽有多愛你。
And I hope that you know
how much your mama loved you.
她總是告訴我你有多特別。
She always told me
how special you were.
你知道，我很感謝你的幫助。
You know, I appreciate the help.
我們就到此為止吧。
Let's just leave it at that.
正確的。
Right.
當他們追你的時候，我當時想，
When they were chasing you,
I was like,
「嘿，別開槍打死那傢伙。他是我的室友。」
"Hey, don't shoot that guy.
He's my roomie."
- 你...你這麼說？ - 是啊，哥們。
- You... You said that?
- Yeah, man.
嘿，你看到你的賞金增加了嗎？
Hey, you see
your bounty went up?
- 我的？- 你的賞金。
- My?
- Your bounty.
離開這裏。
Get outta here.
諾克斯正在戰鬥，夥計。
Knoxx is on the warpath, stud.
你對她做了什麼？老兄？
What'd you do to her, man?
哥們，我有點……有點對她失去理智了，你知道嗎？
Man, I kind of... kind of
ghosted her, you know?
是的，你確實這麼做了，老兄。你對我們所有人都視而不見，老兄。
Yeah, you did, man.
You ghosted all of us, man.
是的。
Yeah.
不管怎樣，老兄，見到你真是太好了。
Anyway, man,
it was really good to see you.
而且你知道，你可以相信我。
And, you know, you can trust me.
我們是朋友，哥們。我不會告訴任何人的。
We're friends, man.
I'm not gonna tell a soul.
哦，拉裏，我不擔心你。
Oh, Larry,
I'm not worried about you.
你是我的男人。
You're my guy.
你是我的主男友。
You're my main man.
我有種感覺，你不會告訴任何人。
I got a feeling you're not
going to tell anybody.
他會沒事嗎？
Is he going to be okay?
嗯，他肯定會宿醉得很厲害。
Well, he'll have
a hell of a hangover.
噢，誰知道電能引發排便？
Ooh, who knew electricity
provoked defecation?
嘿。
Hey.
你們最好趕緊從後門出去。
Y'all better
hustle out the back.
往這邊出去。
Go out this way.
我搞定了這些傢伙。快走。快走。
I got these guys. Go on. Go on.
- 克拉普特拉普，我們走吧。- 繼續走。繼續走。繼續走。
- Claptrap, let's go.
- Go on. Go on. Go on.
你的朋友剛剛喝了大約 10 杯
Your buddy boy here just drank
about 10 shots too many
然後他像一袋土豆一樣倒下了。
then he dropped
like a sack of potatoes.
我想你忘記我了。
I think you forgot me.
嗯。如果能得到小費就更好了。
Mm. And a tip
is always appreciated.
好的。
All right.
看起來就是這樣。
This looks like it.
回聲。
ECHO.
回聲？
ECHO?
確定這就是密碼嗎？
Sure that's the password?
也許你應該回應「ECHO」。
Maybe you gotta echo the "ECHO."
回聲。回聲。
ECHO. ECHO.
好的。
All right.
如果沒有我，你們這些傻瓜就真的會死。
You fools would literally
be dead without me.
- 你需要我。- 開始吧。
- You need me.
-Here we go.
來吧，Claptrap。
Come on, Claptrap.
我們要去哪兒？上去。
Where are we going?
Up.
那麼，你相信這個女人嗎？
So, you trust
this woman?
她是一名外星考古學家，對嗎？
She's a xeno-archaeologist,
all right?
她有點奇怪。
She's a little odd.
但她對保險庫的一切瞭如指掌。
But she knows everything
about the vault.
所以，如果她說了什麼奇怪的話，
So, if she says something weird,
別讓它影響到你，好嗎？
don't let it get to you, okay?
我是10的100次方
I am 10
to the 100th power
對這個地方印象深刻。
impressed with this place.
涼爽的。
Cool.
噢！我看你找到那個女孩了。
Oh! I see you have the girl.
這是正確的。
That's right.
你也找到保險庫鑰匙了嗎？
Did you find
a vault key, too?
你好，我是蒂娜。
Hi, I'm Tina.
很特別的一個。
The special one.
嗯。
Huh.
坦尼斯。
Tannis.
哦。
Oh.
你好，莉莉絲。
Hello, Lilith.
好的，很好。所以你們彼此認識。
Okay, good.
So you guys know each other.
很遺憾。
Unfortunately.
我不留在這裏。
I'm not staying here.
什麼？
What?
好的。
Okay.
但你們聞起來都像脫粒機尿一樣。
But you all smell
like thresher urine.
你的通緝令已經傳遍了全城。
And your wanted poster
just went up all over town.
因此，我建議你們都安頓下來並清理乾淨。
So, I suggest that you all
settle in and clean up.
現在，電淋浴器就在那裏。
Now, the electroshower
is right over there.
噢，淋浴。
Ooh, shower.
嘿，孩子們，我們要走了。走吧。
Hey, kids,
we're out of here. Let's go.
莉莉絲？嘿，我明白了。這裏面有歷史。
Lilith? Hey, I get it.
There's history here.
我甚至不需要知道它是什麼。
I don't even need
to know what it is.
關鍵是她是對的。
The point is that she's right.
如果有我的海報，那就意味著那裏也有你。
If there's a poster of me,
that means there's one of you.
他們正在尋找我們所有人。
They're looking for all of us.
我不想這麼說，但我們別無選擇。
I hate to say it,
but we don't have a choice.
我們必須穩住。
We gotta sit tight.
莉莉絲，我們別無選擇。
Lilith, we don't have a choice.
發生什麼事了，坦尼斯？
What is happening, Tannis?
-電動淋浴器。-等一下。
-Electroshower.
- Wait.
等一下，夥計們。
Wait, guys.
-該洗澡了。- 廢話。
-Time to shower.
- Claptrap.
♪ 該洗澡了 洗澡，該做點什麼了…… ♪
♪ It's time for showering
Showering, time for some... ♪
那不是…不。
That's not... No.
廢話。
Claptrap.
正在重新啟動。
Rebooting.
請大家安靜下來。
Everybody,
just settle down, please.
安家。
Settle down.
嘿，嘿！冷靜下來。
Hey, hey! Settle down.
929,000 的平方根......
Square root of 929,000...
我假設你很沮喪
I am basing my assumption
that you're upset
你的肢體語言。
on your body language.
我看，還是一如既往的敏銳。
Perceptive as ever, I see.
因為你媽媽？
Because of your mother?
呃，不，是因為你。
Uh, no, because of you.
她信任你……
She trusted you...
照顧我。
to take care of me.
但你跑回這裏
But you ran back here
去追尋那個神秘的 Eridian 金庫廢話。
to chase after that mystical
Eridian vault bullshit.
我把你留給了商人。
I left you with tradespeople.
哦。
Oh.
是的。你指的是兇手和小偷
Yes. You mean
the murderers and thieves
在採礦船上。
on the mining ship.
這正是你母親想要的。
It's what your mother wanted.
她想讓我學會如何殺人
She wanted me
to learn how to kill
到 10 歲為止？
by the age of 10?
如何生存。
How to survive.
我必須回到這裏完成她的工作。
I had to come back here
to finish her work.
她相信伊瑞迪安寶庫
She believed the Eridian vault
有能力讓事情變得更好並且......
had the power to change things
for the better and...
她用女兒換來了浪費的時間。
She traded her daughter
for a waste of time.
回到屋裏去。
Go back inside.
這不安全。
It's not safe.
我能照顧好自己。
I can look after myself.
告訴你我很特別。
Told you I'm special.
我們不都是這樣嗎？
Aren't we all?
是的。
Yeah.
他們把我變成這個樣子。
They made me that way.
造詣了你嗎？
Made you?
你是什​​麼意思？
What do you mean?
你的父親是德卡利安·阿特拉斯，
Your father is Deukalian Atlas,
不是嗎？
isn't he?
是也不是。
Yes and no.
不是一個「是或否」的問題。
Not a "yes or no" question.
他是…
He's...
我的...
my...
創建者。
creator.
阿特拉斯 (Atlas) 非常癡迷於金庫。
Atlas is bananapants obsessed
with the vault.
他說只有埃利迪亞的女兒才能打開它。
He says only a daughter
of Eridia can open it.
他找到了保險庫鑰匙的碎片，
He found a piece
of the vault key,
在那件作品上
and on that piece
有一點點……
was a tiny bit...
血液。
of blood.
伊瑞德之血。
Eridian blood.
他克隆了一個伊瑞德人。
He cloned an Eridian.
猜猜那個 Eridian 是誰？
And guess who that Eridian is?
嗯。她叫蒂娜嗎？
Hmm. Is her name Tina?
繁榮。
Boom.
但一切都很好。
But it's all good.
我不在乎我是在實驗室長大的。
I don't care I grew up in a lab.
我從來不想要母親或父親。
I never wanted
a mother or a father.
他創造你是為了打開金庫。
He created you to open a vault.
天啊，真是個混蛋。
God, what an asshole.
這還只是輕描淡寫。
That's an understatement.
他會利用裏面的任何技術
He'll use whatever
technology's inside
並製造超級武器。
and make superweapons.
這傢伙有大問題了。
The dude's got major issues.
對 Atlas 來說我只是一個產品。
I'm just a product to Atlas.
如果他抓住我，
If he gets me,
他要讓我打開保險庫。
he's gonna make me
open the vault.
然後他就會把我關進另一個秘密實驗室
Then he's just gonna lock me up
into another secret lab
並做更多的實驗。
and do more experiments.
如果你看到他們所做的事情
And if you saw
the things they did
對於其他克隆人來說......
to the other clones...
他不會找到你的。
He's not gonna find you.
喲！怎麼了？
Yo! Whassup?
是的！
Yeah!
嘿，那兒有糖片。
Hey, there, sugar chips.
您需要固件更新嗎？
You need a firmware update?
滾開，矮個子。
Piss off, short stuff.
有人需要換油。
Someone needs
an oil change.
我爸爸總是有一句話。
My daddy always had a saying.
永遠不要相信一個不能喝酒的男人。
Never trust a man
who can't hold his liquor.
她電擊了我，好嗎？
She tased me, all right?
我喜歡喝酒。
I love alcohol.
我可以很狂野。
I can be wild.
至於那個小女孩，
As for that little girl,
你不覺得當我看到她時，
you don't think
the second I saw her,
我不會把她交給你
I wouldn't hand her
right over to you
只是為了擺脫你？
just to get rid of you?
我欽佩這場鬥爭，
I admire the fight,
但讓我告訴你接下來會發生什麼。
but let me take you through
what happens next.
備用件！我們封鎖這座城市……
Spare parts!
We seal the city...
誰有我可以使用的備用零件？
Anyone got
spare parts that I can use?
哎呀。
Uh-oh.
嘿，嘿，那是他的機器人。
Hey, hey, that's his robot.
這是一個舊的 CL4P...
It's an old CL4P...
不好意思，我進來了。
Excuse me.
Coming through.
感染了計算機病毒。傳染性極強。
Got a computer virus.
Highly contagious.
清理街道！
Clear the street!
你，倒在地上。
You,
down on the ground.
動起來，動起來，動起來！
Move, move, move!
現在我們有了蒂娜和第一把鑰匙，
Now that we have
Tina and the first key,
我想給你看這個。
I wanna show you this.
這是一本被遺留下來的採礦日誌
This is a mining journal
left behind
由企業官僚制定。
by a corporate bureaucrat.
他對礦工帶回來的所有東西進行了分類，
He cataloged everything
the miners brought in,
大部分都是無用的。
most of it useless.
但在此頁面上...
But on this page...
另一把鑰匙。
Another key.
他認為這只是一塊無用的伊瑞德陶器。
He thought it was a useless
piece of Eridian pottery.
他根本不知道他們找到了保險庫鑰匙。
He had no clue
they'd found a vault key.
這就等於三之二。
That makes two of three.
所以，如果這是第二把鑰匙，
So,
if this is the second key,
為什麼你還沒有它？
why don't you already have it?
因為礦井位於 Caustic Caverns。
Because the mine
is in Caustic Caverns.
媽的。
Oh, shit.
危險！紅色警報！
Danger! Red alert!
大家，我們要行動！士兵們來了！
People, we need to move!
The soldiers, they're coming!
他們有槍！他們正在射擊！
They have guns!
They're shooting!
- 他們開火了！ - 克拉皮，放慢速度。
- They're firing!
- Clappy, slow your roll.
這是什麼交易？
What is the dealio?
真正討厭羅蘭的女兵，
The soldier woman
who really hates Roland,
這表明他們兩個有一些……
which suggests
the two of them had some...
- 來吧，說重點。- 她在酒吧
- Come on, get to the point.
- She was at the bar
審問 Moxxi 和你的朋友 Larry……
interrogating Moxxi
and your friend Larry...
那是他的名字嗎？
Was that his name?
看起來像是一個不錯的室友。
Seemed like a decent roommate.
他們看到你了嗎？
Did they see you?
如果我答應了，你能保證不會生氣嗎？
Do you promise
not to be angry if I say yes?
長矛部隊，封鎖所有出口。
Lance units,
block all exits.
沒有人離開。
No one leaves.
把這個東西拿走。
Get this thing out of here.
摘掉面具。
Masks off.
當然了，指揮官。
Of course, Commander.
當然。嘿！
Of course. Hey!
雙棲定制爆能槍，配備電離射彈。
Double-perched custom Blaster
with ionized projectiles.
這將超過潘多拉上的任何碎骨機。
That'll outpace any
bone shredder on Pandora.
你想交易嗎？
You wanna trade?
我可以給你優惠價，嗯？
I'll give you
special price, huh?
避難所目前已被封鎖。
Sanctuary
is now on lockdown.
在我們找到那個機器人之前，誰也不許去任何地方。
No one goes anywhere
until we find that robot.
有沒有什麼辦法可以離開這裏而不產生垃圾？
Is there any way out of here
that doesn't involve garbage?
一...
Um...
不。
No.
什麼？
What?
你們想用它嗎？
Did you guys wanna use it?
入口就在那些碎片下面。
The entrance is underneath
all of that debris.
在那下面。
Under there.
哇哦！看看我得到了什麼！
Whoo! Look what I got!
嘿！哇，哇，哇。
Hey! Whoa, whoa, whoa.
打開它。
Open it.
你好。
Hello.
你能看看那個嗎？一個梯子。
Would you
look at that? A ladder.
不幸的是，我的設計不利於
Unfortunately,
my design doesn't facilitate
這種垂直旅行。
this type of vertical travel.
德拉茨。
Drats.
我想我只是...
Guess I'll just...
出色地...
Well...
- 命運在等待。 - 我很好！
- Destiny awaits.
-I'm fine!
嗯！肉湯。
Mm! Meat soup.
來自採礦設備的化學廢物。
Chemical waste
from the mining equipment.
它的腐蝕性足以溶解幾乎所有的東西
It's corrosive enough
to dissolve almost anything
除了這個洞穴中的天然水晶。
except the natural crystals
in this cavern.
我們怎樣才能渡過難關？
How are we gonna
get through this?
嗯，事實不會是那樣的。
Well, it's not gonna
be that way.
看來我們得走高速公路了。
Looks like we gotta
take the high road.
戰爭。
Krieg.
讓我們看看是否可以在這裏抓住它。
Let's see if we can
grab this here.
幸運的是我的輪子太大了，
Luckily,
my wheel's too large,
所以我只能看著你們融化
so I'll just watch you all melt
保持安全且合理的距離。
from a safe
and reasonable distance.
你夠小，可以進入那裏。
You are small enough
to get in there.
穿過隧道，
Head through the tunnel,
找到主訪問控制面板，然後解鎖
locate the main access control
panel and then unlock
- 盡頭的門。- 可以做到！
- the door at the end.
-Can do!
- 安靜點。- 沒問題。
- Quietly.
-No problem.
我不希望你們每個人都遭遇任何不幸
I wouldn't want anything bad
to happen to each one of you
以最恐怖的方式。
in the most
horrifying way possible.
好，我先走了。
All right, I'll go first.
- 我明白了。 - 不，我明白了。
- I got this.
- No, I got it.
- 我明白了。-蒂娜！
- I got it.
-Tina!
來了！嘿，嘿。
Coming through!
Hey, hey.
放鬆。
Relax.
我是最輕的。
I'm the lightest.
- 蒂娜！- 嘿！
- Tina!
- Hey!
女士優先。
Ladies first.
如果我這麼做的話，別介意。
Don't mind if I do.
- 你還好嗎？ - 嗯。
- You all right?
- Mm-hmm.
當心。
Be careful.
夥計們。
Guys.
看。
Look.
希望在最奇怪的地方綻放。
Hope blooms
in the strangest places.
有點漂亮。
It's kind of pretty.
任務完成！
Mission accomplished!
門沒有鎖。
The door is unlocked.
♪ 誰最棒？ 我最棒 ♪
♪ Who's the best?
I'm the best ♪
♪ 給我一份工作 我通過了考試 ♪
♪ Give me a job
I pass the test ♪
不能帶他去任何地方。
Can't take him anywhere.
出色地？
Well?
不客氣。
You're welcome.
不可能令人滿意。
Impossible to please.
尖叫淋浴。
Scream showers.
是 Bloodshots。
It's Bloodshots.
是的，他們的符號無處不在。
Yeah, their symbols
are everywhere.
這些是其他精神病患者所害怕的精神病患者。
These are the Psychos
other psychos are afraid of.
他們可能還在這裏。
They're probably still here.
- 我們去看看吧。 - 沒有炸彈。
- Let's go find out.
-  No bombs.
我會進行手術。
I'll be surgical.
這世上只有一個你……
There's only one of you
in the world...
你很特別。
and you're special.
你們坐穩，等我們回來。
You guys sit tight.
Wait for us to come back.
來吧，莉爾。
Come on, Lil.
以前處理過 Bloodshots 嗎？
Dealt with Bloodshots before?
一次。
Once.
你是怎麼擺脫的？
How'd you make it out?
親切的話語和擁抱？
Kind words and hugs?
我不知道他們發生了什麼事
I don't know what it is
that happens to 'em
當他們在這裏的時候
when they're down here
但他們就像被額外劑量的瘋狂擊中了一樣。
but it's like they get hit
with an extra dose of crazy.
剝去肉體，在傷口上撒鹽！
Strip the flesh,
salt the wound!
- 數量太多，無法射擊。 - 或者炸毀？
- There's too many to shoot.
- Or blow up?
嗯，我們確實沒法融入其中。
Well, we can't really blend in.
我們看起來和他們一點都不像。
We don't look
anything like them.
除了你，帥哥。
Except you, handsome.
謝謝你！
Thank you!
根據我的計算，
Well,
according to my calculations,
秘密行動成功的幾率
the odds of a successful
stealth operation
在這種情況下是……
in this scenario is...
0%？哇！
0%? Wow!
你絕對沒見過這樣的情況！
You never see that!
好吧，我想就這樣了。回到卡車上，對吧？
Well, I guess that's it then.
Back to the truck, right?
您是否考慮過干擾因素？
Did you factor in a distraction?
當然。
Of course.
我分析了1600萬個版本
I analyzed 16 million versions
你們其中一人造成了干擾。
where one of you
creates a distraction.
徹底失敗。
Total failure.
不，我們中沒有一個人。
No, not one of us.
等一下，還有誰……？
Wait, who else is...?
哦，不。
Oh, no.
正在通過。
Coming through.
你好呀。
Hi, there.
你好嗎？
How you doing?
只需一點緊張的笑聲就能打破僵局。
Just a little nervous laughter
to crack the ice.
閃亮的！
Shiny!
只是穿過城鎮
Just rolling through town
尋找美好時光。
looking for a good time.
女士們，先生們！
Ladies and gentlemen!
請注意。
Your attention, please.
我來這裏是因為我想
I am here because I want to be
而不是出於更正當的理由
and not for a more
justifiable reason
就像試圖分散注意力一樣。
like trying to be a distraction.
儘管這毫無意義
Even though it makes no sense
讓我說出我想說的話，
for me to say
what I'm about to say,
即使任何理性的人
and even though anyone rational
會懷疑這只是一個粗略計劃的一部分，
would suspect it was just
part of a crude plan,
我決定了
I have decided
以下內容完全由我個人撰寫。
entirely on my own
to say the following.
你們這些婊子應該吃自己的屁股
Y'all bitches
need to eat your own butts
用你的屎嘴……
with your poopy-mouth...
...直到你死於失敗者毒害
...ass-faces until you die
from loser poisoning
就像你這個愚蠢的膿包一樣。
like the stupid
pus-crotches that you is.
是不是太多了？是不是太多了？
Was that too much?
It was too much, wasn't it?
是什麼讓它走向了絕境？
What took it over the edge?
是「滿嘴屎的屁股臉」嗎？
Was it the
"poopy-mouth ass-faces"?
樓梯。來吧！
Stairs. Come on!
不在底盤裏！
Not in the undercarriage!
我的編程...
My programming...
噢，那會留下痕跡的。
Oh, that's gonna leave a mark.
你這個……你成功抓住我了！
Son of a... You got me!
好吧，我死了。那怎麼樣？
Okay, I'm dead. How about that?
他會沒事嗎？
Is he going to be all right?
非常好的計劃。
Excellent plan.
誰會想到他們會向我開槍呢，對吧？
Who would have guessed
they'd shoot me, right?
好吧，我們活了下來。
Well, we survived.
您的 0% 就這麼多。
So much for your 0%.
你還沒出去。
You're not out yet.
我想鑰匙就在這裏。
I think
the key's in here.
甜的。
Sweet.
所以，鑰匙就在其中一個板條箱裏。
So, the key
is in one of these crates.
其中之一
One of these
數以億計的板條箱。
kabillion crates.
是的，這需要一點時間。
Yeah, this is gonna
take a minute.
如果你全天候工作，則需要四天時間
Four days
if you work around the clock
但你做不到，
which you can't,
因為你的身體每16小時就需要休息一次。
because your bodies
require rest every 16 hours.
懶惰的！
Lazy!
如果那些瘋狂的襲擊者先發現我們的話就不會了。
Not if those psycho Raiders
find us first.
那些是血絲。
Those are Bloodshots.
襲擊者住在上面。不住在下面。
Raiders live above.
Not down here.
這裏沒有襲擊者。
There are no Raiders down here.
坦尼斯，沒人談論突擊者隊。
Tannis, nobody's talking
about Raiders.
襲擊者隊有何大不了？
What's the big deal
about Raiders?
我知道，但是你提到了突襲者隊。
I know,
but you brought up Raiders.
咱們就忘掉這件事怎麼樣？
How about
we forget about it?
我這裏遺漏了什麼嗎？
Am I missing
something here?
但我不明白。
But I don't understand.
忘掉突襲者吧！
Forget about
the Raiders!
忘掉它吧。
Just forget about it.
對不起。
I'm sorry.
我明白...
I understand...
- Bloodshots 就在這裏。 - 你一直在提起襲擊者。
- Bloodshots are down here.
- You keep bringing up Raiders.
— 坦尼斯，我向上帝發誓... — 我找到了。
- Tannis, I swear to God...
-I found it.
—什麼？—第二把鑰匙。
- What?
-The second key.
怎麼...怎麼會...?
How... How did...?
我不知道。我猜只是運氣好。
I don't know.
Just lucky, I guess.
是的，我們看看你有多幸運。
Yeah, we'll see
how lucky you are.
我們還是得離開這裏。
We still gotta get out of here.
這邊有一個出口。
There's an exit portal this way.
快點。
Come on.
噓！
Shh!
那是什麼？
What's that?
啥？我在排出多餘的鉛。
What? I'm expelling
the excess lead.
大子彈。大子彈來了。我們走了。
Big bullet. Big bullet coming.
There we go.
你不能再做一次嗎？
Can't you do this another time?
這必須立即發生。
This has to happen now.
別評判我。
Don't judge me.
啥？這有什麼好笑的？
What?
How is this funny?
你小聲點。
You keep it down.
當你烤出一塊麵包時我會評判你嗎？
Do I judge you
when you blast out a loaf?
- 我們不想吸引... - 小心！
- We don't wanna attract...
-Look out!
有一點幫助嗎？
A little help?
來啦！
Incoming!
走吧，走吧！好，現在就走！
Go, go!
Okay, going now!
坦尼斯！
Tannis!
謝謝。
Thank you.
在你的左邊！
On your left!
哇！
Wow!
過來吧，姑娘！
Come here, girlie!
你在幹什麼？
What are you doing?
我需要一把槍。
I needed a gun.
所以你自找的，坦尼斯。問吧！
So you ask for it, Tannis. Ask!
移動！
Move!
這樣！
That way!
夥計們，我們成功了！
We've got this, guys!
沒有我們做不到的事！
There's nothing we can't do!
樓梯！
Stairs!
克裏格，救救我！我沒有……
Krieg, help me! I'm not...
走吧，走吧！
Go, go!
莉莉絲，我抓到你了！
Lilith, I got you!
去！
Go!
羅蘭！
Roland!
小心！
Watch out!
走吧，走吧！
Go, go!
該走了。
Time to go.
我確信我們已經渡過了困難時期。
I'm sure
we're past the hard part.
好的。
Okay.
快走，快走！我們得走了！
Go, go, go!
We gotta move!
放開我！蒂娜！
Let go of me!
Tina!
莉莉絲！你好！
Lilith!
Hello!
跟我來這邊走。
Follow me this way.
我有很強的方向感。
I have a tremendous
sense of direction.
噢，天哪！
Oh, God!
幫我！
Help me!
戰爭，旋轉我！
Krieg, spin me!
我找到了！我找到了！
I found it! I found it!
有電梯！
There's an elevator!
跟我來。這邊走。來吧。
Follow me. This way. Come on.
- 羅蘭！- 克拉皮，快走！快走！快走！
- Roland!
-Clappy, go! Go! Go!
莉莉絲！別再丟下我了！
Lilith!
Don't leave me behind again!
這邊有服務電梯！
There's a service elevator
this way!
它在這兒。
It's up here.
- 這邊走。哦，不。-走！走，走，走！
- This way. Oh, no.
-Go! Go, go, go!
拉屎！
Shit!
這得花點時間。稍等一下。
This is gonna take some time.
Hold this.
廢話！
Claptrap!
我需要幫助！
I need help!
呃，當著大家的面？
Uh,
in front of everyone?
是啊！別往那邊看！
Yes!
Look away!
別往那邊看！我命令你！
Look away! I command you!
克裏格，我們有同伴了。
Krieg, we got company.
流血的時間到了！
It's time to bleed!
- 來吧！- 我正在努力！
- Come on!
- I am trying!
戰爭，等等！
Krieg, wait!
戰爭！
Krieg!
它不起作用。
It's not working.
你不是應該很聰明嗎？
Aren't you supposed
to be smart?
我要把你變成肉自行車！
I'll turn you
into a meat bicycle!
又有一名受害者！
Another victim!
謝謝，孩子。
Thanks, kid.
坦尼斯！
Tannis!
- 我們怎麼樣了？ - 我沒有！
- How we doing?
-I don't have it!
過來，親我一下！
Come here,
give me a kiss!
戰爭！拉回來！
Krieg! Pull back!
走吧！走吧！
Go! Go!
我對一切都感到後悔！
I regret everything!
快點！
Come on!
-我們得走了。-它不起作用。
-We gotta go.
- It's not working.
走吧，坦尼斯。
Go, Tannis.
我們遇到了另一個接線問題。
We have another wiring problem.
嬰兒！
Baby!
拉屎。
Shit.
- 羅蘭，你在做什麼？- 修理它。
- Roland, what are you doing?
-Fixing it.
- 回來！- 嘿。
- Get back here!
-Hey.
不，請不要這樣做。
No. Please don't.
- 羅蘭！ - 嘿，蒂娜。
- Roland!
- Hey, Tina.
我將在保險庫與你見面。
I'll meet you at the vault.
我保證。
I promise.
坦尼斯。
Tannis.
- 擊中！ - 好，擊中！
- Hit it!
- Okay, hitting!
羅蘭！
Roland!
好的，鮑勃。
All right, Bob.
你準備好大幹一場了嗎？
You ready to kick some ass?
我就知道你會這麼說。
I knew you'd say that.
剎車失靈了！我們不會減速！
The brakes are out!
We are not slowing down!
我們不會成功的！
We are not gonna make it!
瞬間移動。
Teleportation.
我可以用我的思想來移動東西，你們。
I can move stuff
with my mind, y'all.
我們還沒死？
We're not dead?
我還被奴役著？糟糕。
I'm still enslaved? Drats.
酸辣醬嘔吐女王。呸！真噁心！
Chutney vomit queen.
Ew! Yuck!
我認為這次瞬間移動讓她病得很重。
I think the teleportation
has made her quite ill.
你是怎麼做到的？
How did you do that?
我不知道。
I don't know.
就這樣發生了。
Just kind of happened.
嘿，羅蘭會沒事的，對吧？
Hey, Roland's
gonna be okay, right?
他是一名精銳士兵。
He's an elite soldier.
如果有人能擺脫這種困境，那就是他。
If anyone can get out of that,
it's him.
我們在哪裏？
Where are we?
我無法讀取 ECHOnet 上的內容。
I can't get a read on ECHOnet.
但看起來我們是在一個舊礦井裏。
But it looks like
we're in an old mine.
也許我們可以在裏面找到一些庇護所。
Maybe we find
some shelter inside.
我已將鑰匙組合起來。
I've combined the keys.
看。
Look.
那是什麼？是地圖嗎？
What's that?
Some kind of a map?
難以置信，不是嗎？
Incredible, isn't it?
它不僅僅是一把鑰匙。
It isn't just a key.
就在那裏...
And right there...
金庫？
The vault?
真可惜
It is a shame
你的媽媽沒有在這裏看到這一切。
your mother is not here
to see this.
它一直在那裏。
It was there the whole time.
顯然。
Apparently.
我以前在某個地方見過這個。
I've seen that
before somewhere.
火鷹。
Firehawk.
伊瑞德女神，星球的保護者。
Eridian goddess,
protector of the planet.
好吧，如果沒有第三件，這一切都毫無意義了。
Well, it's all a bit pointless
without the third piece.
噢，好的，我們有了。
Oh, well, we have it.
她就是關鍵。
She's the key.
電梯證實了這一點。
The elevator confirmed it.
那是一次階段性行走。
That was a phasewalk.
只有伊瑞德人才能做到這一點。
Only an Eridian could do that.
等一下。
Wait a minute.
如果她是鑰匙的一部分，
If she's a piece of the key,
當她打開它時會發生什麼？
what happens when she opens it?
我以為你知道。
I assumed you knew.
你媽媽從來沒有告訴過你嗎？
Did your mother never tell you?
我當時八歲。我幾乎記不起她的臉了。
I was eight. I can barely
remember her face.
當埃利迪亞的女兒把鑰匙放進去時，
When the daughter of Eridia
places the key,
碎片被消耗後保險庫就會打開。
the pieces are consumed
and the vault opens.
現在，我不一定相信這意味著殺死她。
Now, I don't necessarily
believe that means kill her.
但您已準備好承擔這個風險。
But you're prepared
to take that risk.
好吧，我們別無選擇。
Well, we have no choice.
我們要麼帶她去
Either we take her
或者 Atlas 也可以。
or Atlas does.
沒有犧牲就沒有救贖。
There is no salvation
without sacrifice.
史上最糟糕的群交。
Worst orgy ever.
安息吧，鮑勃。
Rest in peace, Bob.
媽的。
Oh, shit.
哇哦。抱歉。
Whoa. Sorry.
我一時還以為你是屍僵了。
I thought for a moment there
you had rigor mortis.
那真是一個美好的時刻。
It was a really nice moment.
我會永遠珍惜它。
I'll treasure it always.
此外，我還找到了我需要的最後零件
Also, I scavenged
the final parts I needed
來自一個壞掉的變壓器，
from a dead transformer,
並修復了被你魯莽毀壞的東西。
and fixed the thing
you so recklessly destroyed.
您沒有按這個吧？
You didn't press this, did you?
我沒有。
I did not.
如果你願意的話我可以再次將其粉碎。
I can crush it again
if you'd like.
哦，「謝謝你，Claptrap。你太重要了。」
Oh, "Thank you, Claptrap.
You're indispensable."
謝謝你，莉莉絲。你的讚美溫暖了我的心靈。
Thank you, Lilith.
Your praise warms my soul.
莉莉絲。
Lilith.
你弄壞了我給你的信標嗎？
Have you broken the beacon
I gave you?
啊，這東西一直都是垃圾。
Ah, this thing was junk
the whole time.
一點也不。
Not at all.
這是一個高度精確的跟蹤裝置
It was a highly accurate
tracking device
這讓我直接認識了你和蒂娜。
that has led me
right to you and Tina.
現在我開始思考
Now, I was beginning to think
她將永遠躲避我。
that she would
elude me forever.
她很聰明。
She's smart.
她是我的。
She is mine.
還有赤紅之槍
And the Crimson Lance
正在去接她的路上。
are on their way
to collect her now.
如果你來追她，我就會毀掉鑰匙。
If you come after her,
I'll destroy the key.
不，你不會的。
No, you won't.
因為如果你這麼做了，
Because if you did,
那麼我就得殺了
then I would have to kill
其餘的英雄獵人
the rest of that heroic band
of vault hunters
她一直在和貧民窟的人在一起。
she's been
slumming around with.
我向你保證，莉莉絲，
And I promise you, Lilith,
他們不會很快死去。
they won't be quick deaths.
好的。
Good.
很高興看到你
Glad to see you making
一次明智的選擇。
the smart choice for once.
當這一切結束後，
And when this is over,
您將獲得我們約定的報酬。
you'll be paid
what we agreed on.
謝謝你，莉莉絲。
Thank you, Lilith.
哦。
Oh.
蒂娜，你看，我知道這看起來怎麼樣，但是......
Tina, look, I know
how this must look, but...
我是唯一一個可以打開保險庫的人。
I'm the only one
who can open the vault.
我要用裏面的東西殺死他。
And I'm gonna use whatever
is inside to kill him.
可惜您沒能親眼見證這一切。
Too bad you won't
be around to see it.
- 等一下。- 享受你的自由。
- Wait.
- Enjoy your freedom.
蒂娜。蒂娜，不！
Tina. Tina, no!
我跳舞是因為...
I'm dancing because...
你還活著。
you're alive.
並不是因為我以為你已經死了。
Not because
I thought you were dead.
令人暖心。
Heartwarming.
其他人在哪兒？
Where are the others?
他們在村子裏找到一輛卡車然後離開。
They found a truck
in the village and left.
沒有我。
Without me.
哪個村子？
What village?
這肯定是原創的
This must have
been one of the original
潘多拉定居點。
Pandoran settlements.
多麼古雅啊。
How quaint.
我知道這個地方。
I know this place.
來吧，來吧，別再說了。
Come on.
Come on. Leave it.
來吧，親愛的。
Come on, sweetie.
快把莉莉絲給我！
Hurry, give me Lilith!
加油！加油！
Come on! Come on!
記住我會永遠愛你！
Remember I will always love you!
媽媽！
Mama!
不！
No!
嘿，你要去哪兒？
Hey,
where are you going?
莉莉絲。
Lilith.
莉莉絲！
Lilith!
這是你的家嗎？
Is this your home?
是的。
Yeah.
我曾經住在這裏。
I used to live here once.
這個地方是...
This place is...
讓我回想起文件深處的一些東西。
reminiscent of something
deep in my files.
那幅畫……
That drawing...
我感覺很奇怪。
I feel strange.
莉莉絲。
Lilith.
媽媽？
Mom?
如果您看到這個...
If you're seeing this...
我恐怕沒能成功。
I'm afraid I didn't make it.
我很抱歉把你送走了。
I'm so sorry
that I sent you away.
我不想。
I didn't want to.
但我很快就意識到
But as soon as I realized
你是什​​麼，
what you are,
你可能會成為什麼……
what you might become...
我知道在潘多拉星球上你永遠不會安全。
I knew you'd never
be safe here on Pandora.
但如果你回來的話，
But if you ever return,
我確信 Claptrap 會找到你，
I've made sure
that Claptrap will find you,
幫助你理解...
help you understand...
你的命運。
your destiny.
莉莉絲，我愛你。
Lilith, I love you.
我希望……
I wish...
我可以最後一次擁抱你。
I could hold you one last time.
蒂娜！
Tina!
哇哦。這太奇怪了。
Whoa.
That was weird.
我昏了過去。
I blacked out.
是不是發生什麼重要的事情了？
Did something important happen?
它說它就在這裏。
It's saying it's here.
我看到的只是一些洞。
All I'm seeing
is some holes.
你確定就是這個嗎？
Are you sure this is it?
我不知道。它在某個地方。
I don't know.
It's somewhere.
好的，它看起來像什麼？
Okay,
what does it look like?
很大。是拱門。
Big. It's an arch.
它就在這兒的某個地方。我知道它就在這兒。
It's here somewhere.
I know it's here.
你怎麼知道它在這裏？
How do you know it's here?
因為我感受到情感。
Because I'm feeling emotion.
你能更具體一點嗎？
Can you be more specific?
- 力量！- 現在不行，克裏格。求你了。
- Thing of power!
- Not right now, Krieg. Please.
- 好的，我明白了... - 但這意味著什麼！
- Okay, I get it...
- But that means something!
不，不，不！
No, no, no!
我沒有關注。
I'm not following.
克裏格，你真是個天才。你找到了！
Krieg, you genius. You found it!
我得警告你，這可能會要了你的命。
I have to warn you,
this might kill you.
我？
Me?
不，孩子。我才是特別的一個。
Nah, kid. I'm the special one.
無論這是什麼，它都會讓我變得無敵。
Whatever this is,
it's gonna make me invincible.
剛才發生了什麼？
What just happened?
我是特別的一個。它應該做點什麼。
I'm the special one.
It should do something.
顯然不是。
Apparently not.
幹得好，蒂娜。
Well done, Tina.
做得好。
Well done.
令人驚奇的努力。
Amazing effort.
你在銀河系最糟糕的星球上倖存了下來。
You survived the worst planet
in the galaxy.
你找到了鑰匙和保險庫本身。
You found the key
and the vault itself.
你讓你的父親感到非常驕傲。
You've made your father
so proud.
諾克斯指揮官，
Commander Knoxx,
我需要她的神經系統完好無損。
I need
her nervous system intact.
將器官放在冰上。
Keep the organs on ice.
也許下一個克隆人會給我們帶來更好的運氣。
Perhaps we'll have better luck
with the next clone.
嘿，混蛋。
Hey, asshole.
羅蘭，你的出場可真是精彩啊。
That was quite
an entrance, Roland.
你想念我？
You miss me?
如果不是因為……你也許已經挽救了局面。
You might have saved the day
if it wasn't for...
我的 Atlas 汽車防護罩。
my Atlas auto shield.
把他們全部殺掉。
Kill them all.
不要開火。
Hold your fire.
這是命令。
That's an order.
您聽到了指揮官的話。
You heard the commander.
武器放下。
Weapons down.
羅蘭，你說得對。
Roland, you were right.
我應該...
I should've...
不！
No!
還有其他異議嗎？
Any other objections?
僅一個！
Just one!
你繼續呼吸。
That you continue breathing.
但我會允許
But I'll allow it
如果你能讓我的朋友平安地離去。
if you let my friends
go in peace.
告訴我，莉莉絲，
And tell me, Lilith,
我為什麼要這麼做？
just why would I do that?
因為我是埃利迪亞的女兒。
Because I'm the daughter
of Eridia.
我以前在某個地方見過這個。
I've seen that
before somewhere.
火鷹。
Firehawk.
伊瑞迪安女神。
Eridian goddess.
這是你的星球，莉莉絲。
It's your planet, Lilith.
你必須保護它。
You have to protect it.
媽媽愛你。
Mama loved you.
她總是告訴我你有多特別。
She always told me
how special you were.
我找到了。
I found it.
怎麼會......？ 我不知道。
How did...?
I don't know.
我想，只是運氣好而已。
Just lucky, I guess.
埃利迪亞的女兒，寶貝！
Daughter of Eridia, baby!
我敢打賭你沒想到這一點！
Bet you didn't see that coming!
但...
But...
但我卻是特別的一個。
But I'm the special one.
噢，是的。
Oh, you are.
只是和你想像的不一樣。
Just not the way you thought.
我打開保險庫……
I open the vault...
女孩自由了。
the girl goes free.
你打開保險庫
You open the vault
你們都可以自由了。
and you all go free.
我向你保證。
You have my word.
我剛剛明白了。
I just figured it out.
你媽媽把你給了我
Your mother gave you to me
帶你離開這裏，
to take you away from here,
所以你就不需要打開那個保險庫。
so you would never
have to open that vault.
嗯，結果非常好。
Well, that worked out great.
我必須打開它。
I have to open it.
沒有犧牲就沒有救贖。
No salvation without sacrifice.
記住？
Remember?
但你不能。
But you can't.
你不能。
You can't.
沒有什麼。
It's fine.
你很安全。
You're safe.
蒂娜，
And, Tina,
記憶更加強大
memories are more powerful
比 Atlas 所能創造的任何東西都要多。
than anything
Atlas could ever create.
現在，你得到我的一個了。
Now, you got one of me.
是的。
Yes.
坦尼斯，發生什麼事了？
Tannis, what's happening?
伊瑞德人拯救了我們
The Eridians have delivered us
冠軍。
a champion.
傳說是真的。
The legends were true.
她是火鷹。
She's the Firehawk.
莉莉絲，你能聽到我的聲音嗎？
Lilith, can you hear me?
帶我進金庫。
Take me into the vault.
如果你不這樣做，我就要傷害你的朋友了。
If you won't, I'm going
to have to hurt your friends.
拉我上去！
Pull me up!
莉莉絲，救命！
Lilith, help!
讓雨下吧，蒂娜！
Make it rain, Tina!
攻擊！
Attack!
你們在射擊嗎？
Are you guys shooting?
抱歉，我什麼也沒感覺到。
I'm sorry,
I didn't feel a thing.
你中槍了。你中槍了。
You get a bullet.
跑，跑。
Run, run.
星際忍者刺客模式已激活。
Interplanetary
ninja assassin mode activated.
讓開，賤人。
Step aside, bitches.
莉莉絲。莉莉絲！
Lilith. Lilith!
不！
No!
莉莉絲，你能聽到我的聲音嗎？
Lilith, can you hear me?
好吧，只要它持續下去，就很有趣。
Well, it was fun
while it lasted.
莉莉絲。來吧，莉莉絲。
Lilith. Come on, Lilith.
莉莉絲。
Lilith.
請你醒醒。
Please wake up.
坦尼斯，快跑。
Tannis, run.
除了我自己沒人能殺我！
Nobody kills me but me!
大家快跑！
Everybody, run!
快走！快走！
Go! Move, move!
拉屎！
Shit!
坦尼斯，你還活著。
Tannis, you're alive.
我還活著！
I'm alive!
這傢伙，不太一樣。
This guy, not so much.
警報器響了。
A siren.
蒂娜！
Tina!
坦尼斯，蒂娜在哪兒？
Tannis, where's Tina?
莉莉絲！
Lilith!
我警告過你不要讓我失望。
I warned you
not to disappoint me.
現在帶我去金庫。
Take me to the vault now.
好吧，該死。
Well, shit.
放開我！
Let go of me!
繼續掙扎的話我就殺了你。
Keep struggling
and I'll kill you.
莉莉絲！
Lilith!
莉莉絲，展現你自己吧！
Lilith, show yourself!
現身吧，不然我就殺了她！
Show yourself or I kill her!
我會做到的！
I'll do it!
相信我。
Believe me.
噢，我相信你。
Oh, I believe you.
啊，莉莉絲。
Ah, Lilith.
這是...
This is...
難以置信。
unbelievable.
比我想像的還要多。
So much more
than I ever imagined.
曾經統治過銀河系的種族的寶藏。
The treasures of a race
who once ruled the galaxies.
看。
Look.
那股力量。你能感受到嗎？
The power. Can you feel it?
你可以嗎...
Can you...
是的，我能感覺到。
Yeah, I can feel it.
說實話，這讓我有點噁心。
Honestly, it makes me
a little sick.
你會習慣的。
You'll get used to it.
是的。你看……
Yeah. You see...
我擁有一些像你這樣的男人永遠無法擁有的東西。
I have something that a man
like you will never have.
足夠的。
Enough.
莉莉絲。在這兒。
Lilith.
Over here.
丟了東西？
Lose something?
蒂娜！
Tina!
噠噠。
Ta-da.
再見。
Bye-bye.
不，莉莉絲。
No, Lilith.
- 莉莉絲，求你了。- 別擔心。
- Lilith, please.
-Don't worry.
在這裏你不會感到孤獨。
You won't get lonely down here.
不不。
No. No.
不，不，不。不！
No, no, no. No!
莉莉絲！蒂娜！
Lilith! Tina!
不，不，不！
No, no, no!
♪ 就像糖一樣 ♪
♪ It's like sugar ♪
♪ 太甜蜜了 ♪
♪ So sweet ♪
不好意思！我進來了。
Excuse me!
Coming through.
為英雄讓路！
Make way for the hero!
嘿。
Hey.
你聽見了嗎？
You hear that?
什麼？
What?
我想，這就是和平的聲音。
That I think is what
peace sounds like.
好好享受。
Enjoy it.
讓我們讓它持續下去。
Let's make it last.
我給你泡了一點茶。
I made you a little tea.
我以為你可能有點脫水。
I thought you might be
a little dehydrated.
好的，各位。讓我們，嗯...
All right, guys. Let's, um...
我們去參加聚會吧。
Let's join the party.
好極了！太棒了！
All right! Hooray!
哎呀，慶祝得太早了。
Whoops. Premature celebration.
這種事以前從來沒有發生過。
That's never happened before.
你準備好了嗎？
You ready?
我們將在那裏與你見面。
We'll meet you there.
我接到你了。
I got you.
來吧，戰爭。
Come on, Krieg.
該去喝個酩酊大醉了。
Time to go get drunk.
盛大的肉食盛宴。
Glorious meat fiesta.
所以...
So...
呃…
Uh...
我不這麼認為。
I don't think so.
快點。
Come on.
做那件事。
Do the thing.
我覺得我有點老了，
I'm a bit old, I think,
為了取悅你們而把自己點燃。
to be setting myself on fire
for your amusement.
你知道你想要。
You know you want to.
讓我告訴你一切
Let me
tell you everything
您需要瞭解有關潘多拉的知識。
you need to know about Pandora.
她很危險。
She's dangerous.
她很髒。
She's dirty.
她絕對是個有毒廢物傾倒場。
And she's definitely
a toxic waste dump.
但她是我的家。
But, she's my home.
真是炫耀。
What a show-off.
♪ 如果邪惡對我下手 ♪
♪ If evil lays
Its hands on me ♪
♪ 點亮一點光芒 照亮我的靈魂 ♪
♪ Shine a little light
On my soul ♪
♪ 讓我看到我看不到的東西 ♪
♪ Show me things I cannot see ♪
♪ 點亮一點光芒 照亮我的靈魂 ♪
♪ Shine a little light
On my soul ♪
♪ 如果邪惡對我下手 ♪
♪ If evil lays
Its hands on me ♪
♪ 點亮一點光芒 照亮我的靈魂 ♪
♪ Shine a little light
On my soul ♪
♪ 我等待著，耐心祈禱 ♪
♪ I'm waiting, praying
Patiently ♪
♪ 點亮一點光芒 照亮我的靈魂 ♪
♪ Shine a little light
On my soul ♪
♪ 如果邪惡對我下手 ♪
♪ If evil lays
Its hands on me ♪
♪ 點亮一點光芒 照亮我的靈魂 ♪
♪ Shine a little light
On my soul ♪
♪ 讓我看到我看不到的東西 ♪
♪ Show me things I cannot see ♪
♪ 點亮一點光芒 照亮我的靈魂 ♪
♪ Shine a little light
On my soul ♪
♪ 讓我看到我看不到的東西 ♪
♪ Show me things I cannot see ♪
♪ 點亮一點光芒 照亮我的靈魂 ♪
♪ Shine a little light
On my soul ♪
♪ 如果邪惡對我下手 ♪
♪ If evil lays
Its hands on me ♪
♪ 點亮一點光芒 照亮我的靈魂 ♪
♪ Shine a little light
On my soul ♪
♪ 我等待著，耐心祈禱 ♪
♪ I'm waiting, praying
Patiently ♪
哇喔！看看這些動作。
Woo-hoo! Check these moves.
我來跳舞啦，小子。
I come to dance, mofo.
扭動身體。現在就鍛煉。
Twerk it. Work it out, now.
做 Claptrap。這是我的……
Do the Claptrap. It's my...
哦，嘿！嘿，等等！不，不，不！
Oh, hey! Hey, wait! No, no, no!
這是怎麼回事？不！
What's goin' on here? No!
這是我的復活節彩蛋！
It's my Easter egg!
啊！你這個混蛋……
Ah! You son of a...
別讓我離開！
Don't make me leave!
當我給予人們他們想要的東西時，情況並非如此！
Not when I'm giving the people
what they want!